Hazman Harif

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name Hazman Bin Harif Fadilah Address Kuala Terengganu, Terengganu

Telephone 0169257939

E-mail hazmanhariff@gmail.com

Age 29

PROFILE

Passionate Geologist majoring in mineral exploration and green mining technology. I study and research rare earth minerals detection using geoelectrical and FBG hybrid technology. I also have experience in designing in situ leaching models for sustainable mining in the future. With recent experiences and skills, I am looking forward to joining an organization that provides room and relentless opportunities for growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1/2023 - 6/2024: Geoscience Officer

Permint Granite Sdn Bhd, Kuala Terengganu, Terengganu

Responsible for mineral exploration and mining activities in Terengganu mainly in silica sand and gold mining.

- Geological mapping for potential mineral exploration
- · Mineral analysis and reserve estimation for economical mining
- · Supervising silica sand washing plant operation
- Overseeing of alluvial gold processing
- GIS application for mining data management

6/2021 - 12/2022: Geologist

Spin Eight Nano Technologies Sdn Bhd, *Ipoh*, *Perak* Responsible for rare earth minerals in Perak under MB Inc.

- Research in rare earth minerals detection using FBG technology
- Identify and assess potential location for for lanthanides detection
- · Collect and analyze soil samples for mineral exploration
- Design in situ leaching plant for rare earth elements extraction

6/2018 - 5/2021: Sales Executive

HAK Ventures Sdn Bhd, Kuala Terengganu, Terengganu Involved in the finance and money services business industry

- Served more than 20,000 customers in money services
- Secured RM 1 million sales per month
- Conduct KYC, CDD and STR to adhere with AML/CFT

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018	Bachelor of Technology (Hons) Petroleum Geoscience Universiti Teknologi Petronas
2013 - 2014	Foundation in Science Universiti Teknologi Petronas
2008 - 2012	SPM SM Imtiaz Kuala Terengganu

COMPETENCIES

Computer skills:

Fully comprehensive with the following software:

- MS Office
- Google Earth Pro
- ArcGIS
- Petrel
- Video Editing Software

Languages:

Fully fluent in speaking and writing with the following language:

- English
- Malay

REFERENCES

- Tuan Mohd Azizi | Senior Geologist Permint Granite Sdn Bhd (azizi@permintgranite.com.my / 0167940934)
- Thenesh A/L Sevoo | Manager Spin Eight Nano Technologies Sdn Bhd (thenesh@spineight.com / 0174252792)